Register of the John Davenport Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- SUBJECT FILE, 1965-1987
  - Rhodesia
    - Remarks by Senator George McGovern, 1978 (Folder 48: 2)
    - Report by Robert Morris, 1978 November 24 (Folder 48: 3)
    - Writing by Robert Moss, "Rhodesia: Memo to Dr. Owen," 1978 May (Folder 48: 4)
  - Rhodesia - Foreign relations - Great Britain (Folder 48: 5)
  - Rhodesian Constitutional Commission. Report, 1968 (Folder 48: 6)
  - Rhodesian Information Office, Washington, D.C. (Folder 48: 7)
  - Rhodesian National Farmers' Union (Folder 48: 8)
  - Ryukyu Islands., See Okinawa
  - School integration - United States (Folder 48: 9)
  - Shadow Open Market Committee (Folder 48: 10)
  - Social security - United States (Folder 48: 11)
  - Socialism - India (Folder 48: 12)
  - South Africa (Folder 48: 13-14)
  - South Africa (Box-folder 49: 1-6)
  - South Africa (Box-folder 50: 1-6)
  - South Africa (Box-folder 51: 1-7)
  - South Africa (Box-folder 52: 1-4)
  - South Africa (Box-folder 53: 1-5)
  - South Africa (Box-folder 54: 1)
  - South Africa - Relations with the United States, 1966 (Folder 54: 2)
  - South Africa Foundation (Folder 54: 3)
  - South Africa Foundation Information Digest, 1977-1979 (Folder 54: 4)
  - South African Digest, 1976-1979 (Folder 54: 5)
  - Southern Africa Freedom Foundation, "Position Paper," 1977-1986 (Folder 54: 6)
  - South West African Peoples Organization, 1981 (Folder 54: 7)
  - Southwest Africa (Folder 54: 8)
  - Southwest Africa (Box-folder 55: 1-2)
  - Sternlight, Peter (Folder 55: 3)
  - Strauss, Leo (Folder 55: 4)
  - Student movements - United States (Folder 55: 5-6)
  - Taxation
    - International (Folder 55: 7)
    - United States (Folder 55: 8-9)
  - Telluride Association (Folder 55: 10)
  - Time, Inc. Remarks by J. Davenport for meeting, n.d. (Folder 55: 11)
  - Unemployment - United States (Folder 55: 12)
  - Vietnam - Foreign relations - United States (Folder 55: 13)
  - Von Mises, Ludwig (Folder 55: 14)
  - Wages - United States (Box-folder 56: 1-3)
  - Welfare economics (Folder 56: 4)
  - World economy, 1980-1982 (Folder 56: 5)
  - Zimbabwe
    - General (Folder 56: 6-8)
    - Economic conditions (Box-folder 57: 1)
    - Economic policy (Folder 57: 2)
  - Miscellany (Folder 57: 3-6)
- WRITINGS BY OTHERS, 1961-1980 (Box 58-60)
  - General (Folder 57: 7)
  - Arendt, Hannah (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - Audoin, Raoul (Folder 58: 2)
  - Backman, Jules (Folder 58: 3)
  - Ballou, F. William (Folder 58: 4)
  - Barker, I. L. (Folder 58: 5)
  - Berkman, Neil G. (Folder 58: 6)
  - Bradley, Philip D. (Folder 58: 7)
  - Brandt, Karl (Folder 58: 8)
  - Brozen, Yale (Folder 58: 9)
  - Brzeski, Andrzej (Folder 58: 10)
  - Buchanan, James M. (Folder 58: 11)
  - Burton, John (Folder 58: 12)
  - Cagan, Phillip (Folder 58: 13)
  - Chambers, Whittaker (Folder 58: 14)
  - Ellis, Albert (Folder 58: 15)
  - Emminger, Otmar (Folder 58: 16)
  - Exter, John (Folder 58: 17)
  - Faltermayer, Ed (Folder 58: 18)
  - Feldstein, Martin (Folder 58: 19)
  - Friedman, Milton (Folder 58: 20-21)
  - Fuchs, Victor (Folder 58: 22)
  - Gay, Peter (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - Glazier, William (Folder 59: 2)
  - Gray, John (Folder 59: 3)
  - Grimond, Jo, Lord (Folder 59: 4)
  - Haggard, Thomas R. (Folder 59: 5)
  - Havender, William (Folder 59: 6)
  - Hayek, Friedrich A. von (Folder 59: 7)
  - Henry, Paul B. (Folder 59: 8)
  - Herberg, Will (Folder 59: 9)
  - Jaffa, Harry V. (Folder 59: 10)
  - Jewkes, John (Folder 59: 11)
  - Johnson, Paul (Folder 59: 12)
  - Jones, Homer (Folder 59: 13)
  - Jouvenel, Bertrand de (Folder 59: 14)
  - Kemp, Arthur (Folder 59: 15)
  - Kristol, Irving (Folder 59: 16)
  - Kuehnelt-Leddihn, Erik von (Folder 59: 17)
  - Laffer, Arthur (Folder 59: 18)
  - Lentz, Bernard F. (Folder 59: 19)
  - Letwin, Shirley Robin (Folder 59: 20)
  - Loescher, Samuel (Folder 59: 21)
  - Luce, Henry R. (Folder 59: 22)
  - Machlup, Fritz (Folder 59: 23)
  - McLaughlin, Donald (Folder 59: 24)
  - Molsberger, Josef (Folder 59: 25)
  - Moore, William J. (Folder 59: 26)
  - Morse, Jeremy (Folder 59: 27)
  - Nishiyama, Chiaki (Folder 59: 28)
  - O'Connell, Francis A. (Folder 59: 29)
  - Olsen, Leif H. (Folder 59: 30)
  - Petro, Sylvester (Folder 60: 1)
  - Powledge, Fred (Folder 60: 2)
  - Regnery, Henry (Folder 60: 3)
  - Ricardo-Campbell, Rita (Folder 60: 4)
  - Roche, John P. (Folder 60: 5)
  - Roepke, Wilhelm (Folder 60: 6)
  - Rostow, Eugene V. (Folder 60: 7-8)
  - Saulnier, Raymond (Folder 60: 9)
  - Seldon, Arthur (Folder 60: 10)
  - Seuss, Wilhelm (Folder 60: 11)
  - Shenfield, Arthur (Folder 60: 12)
  - Stigler, George (Folder 60: 13)
  - Stillman, C. L. (Folder 60: 15)
  - Terborgh, George (Folder 60: 16)
  - Tumlir, Jan (Folder 60: 17)
  - Tyrmand, Leopold (Folder 60: 18)
  - Van den Haag, Ernest (Folder 60: 19)
  - Von Mises, Ludwig (Folder 60: 20)
  - Walker, Michael (Folder 60: 21)
  - Wallich, Henry C. (Folder 60: 22)
  - Wanninski, Jude (Folder 60: 23)
  - Weintraub, Robert E. (Folder 60: 24)
  - Wilhelmsen, Frederick (Folder 60: 25)
  - Willes, Mark H. (Folder 60: 26)
  - Wolfe, Robert Paul (Folder 60: 27)
  - Wright, David M. (Folder 60: 28)
  - Yeager, Leland (Folder 60: 29)